<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)</title><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45093192</link><description>Hacker News RSS</description><docs>https://hnrss.org/</docs><generator>hnrss v2.1.1</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 14:56:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hnrss.org/whoishiring/jobs?count=50&amp;q=San%20Francisco" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by betsyy in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>RBF Capital | San Francisco, CA | ONSITE | Full-time<p>Quantamental hedge fund with a 25+ year winning track record; small, under-the-radar; direct access to principals.<p>Building an internal data lake and AI/ML agentic RAG platform to make market, SEC, and alt-data instantly searchable.<p>Hiring:<p>(priority) Lead AI Platform Engineer: Design data platform architecture with ingestion pipelines, storage layers, and modern stacks; Build ML workflows for automated analysis and pattern recognition<p>Financial Engineer: Architect industry-specific quantitative models and factor definitions; Define and oversee rigorous model validation to ensure financial accuracy<p>View full job descriptions and apply at rbfcapital.com<p>My LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/betsy-alter/" rel="nofollow">https://www.linkedin.com/in/betsy-alter/</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:51:55 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45202718</link><dc:creator>betsyy</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45202718</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45202718</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by sarahweavebio in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Weave Platform (<a href="https://www.weave.bio/" rel="nofollow">https://www.weave.bio/</a>) | San Francisco, CA | HYBRID | FULLTIME<p>Regulatory AI SaaS for Biotech | Weave Bio is a <50 person start-up building an AI-native regulatory automation management platform redefining regulatory submissions for novel therapeutic candidates.<p>Hiring: - Senior Backend Engineer (Django + Python + Postgres + Redis + production LLMs)<p>- Senior Frontend Engineering (Typescript + React)<p>- Senior AI Engineer (Data Scientist + Edu in Bio/Chem/Med)<p>- AI Research Scientist<p>- Product Marketing Manager<p>Apply here: <a href="https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/weave" rel="nofollow">https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/weave</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:14:35 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45182238</link><dc:creator>sarahweavebio</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45182238</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45182238</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by tdquang in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>FleetWorks | Onsite, San Francisco | FleetWorks is rebuilding the $1 trillion freight marketplace with AI.<p>Every year, companies spend over a trillion dollars moving freight across the U.S. — but the system for matching trucks with jobs is still slow, manual, and fragmented. FleetWorks is fixing that.<p>We’re turning today’s chaotic freight market into a modern, intelligent marketplace — one where AI agents replace the endless phone calls, texts and emails and match jobs to trucks instantly.<p>Focus Open Roles:<p>- Software Engineer<p>- Lead Designer<p><a href="https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/FleetWorks" rel="nofollow">https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/FleetWorks</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 02:42:49 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45176788</link><dc:creator>tdquang</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45176788</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45176788</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by devinbhushan in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Squint | Onsite, San Francisco | Squint is a mobile app that uses AI and AR to automate data entry, generate custom procedures, and make every operator an expert.<p>Squint is the leading manufacturing intelligence platform. We unlock agentic manufacturing by giving frontline operators the knowledge they need, exactly when they need it.<p>We build consumer-grade software that delivers enterprise-grade impact — on the devices people already know and trust: phones and tablets. By combining cutting-edge tech with thoughtful customer insight we’re transforming how the physical world works.<p>High Priority Open Roles:<p>- Product Engineer, High Velocity<p>- Senior GTM Recruiter<p>- Strategic Enterprise Account Executive<p>- Account Director, Large Enterprise<p>- SDR Manager<p>- Go-To-Market Engineer<p>View full list of roles and apply here: <a href="https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/squint.ai?utm_source=Hackernews" rel="nofollow">https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/squint.ai?utm_source=Hackernews</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:46:38 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45169753</link><dc:creator>devinbhushan</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45169753</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45169753</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by chicagobuss in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Duckbill engineering is hiring a full-time ONSITE full-stack senior SWE in downtown San Francisco. We WFH Tuesdays and Thursdays.<p>We're tackling the hardest finops challenges for the biggest enterprise customers head-on and have a killer team along with the advantage of the established and industry-leading DuckBill Group.<p>Help shape the leading edge of an entire industry with us while we're still just at seed stage and under 6 engineers!<p>Comp range is generous on the equity and between 180k and 200k base depending on seniority. We're cooking with flask, react, postgres, and clickhouse on AWS at the moment.<p>---<p>Apply here: <a href="https://www.duckbillgroup.com/careers/" rel="nofollow">https://www.duckbillgroup.com/careers/</a><p>Or email:  careers@duckbillhq.com</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 21:04:28 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45152815</link><dc:creator>chicagobuss</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45152815</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45152815</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by untolabs in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Unto Labs | San Francisco, CA | ONSITE (Hybrid OK), REMOTE (US) | Full-Time<p>Unto Labs is developing the Thru Layer-1 blockchain (<a href="https://thru.org" rel="nofollow">https://thru.org</a>)<p>We recently announced $14.4 million in funding to make blockchains & digital assets useful for the world. Founded by Jump Crypto alumni and core contributors to the Solana protocol and the Firedancer client (<a href="https://github.com/firedancer-io/firedancer" rel="nofollow">https://github.com/firedancer-io/firedancer</a>), we’re tackling fundamental scalability, performance, and usability challenges in distributed ledgers.<p>Our runtime conforms to the RISC-V specification—moving away from domain-specific VMs, DSLs, and bespoke compiler toolchains that limit developer and institutional adoption. You can write smart contracts and programs in any LLVM compatible programming language and reason about a standard ISA in RISC-V. Components are developed in C for maximal control over performance and resource usage.<p>We believe there is a unique window of opportunity to developer fairer, more accessible, and more global financial products on resilient public blockchains.<p>We are hiring for the following roles:<p>- Systems Engineer: <a href="https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/unto-labs/13df6bea-b253-4c80-ae05-5" rel="nofollow">https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/unto-labs/13df6bea-b253-4c80-ae05-5</a>...<p>- Design Engineer: <a href="https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/unto-labs/81cbbb75-a75a-4d96-b5da-7" rel="nofollow">https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/unto-labs/81cbbb75-a75a-4d96-b5da-7</a>...<p>- Product Engineer: <a href="https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/unto-labs/1ae2769b-1a67-41e2-a8d6-5" rel="nofollow">https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/unto-labs/1ae2769b-1a67-41e2-a8d6-5</a>...</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 03:59:05 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45112138</link><dc:creator>untolabs</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45112138</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45112138</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by hahnbee in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Mintlify | Senior SWE | Onsite San Francisco
Mintlify is a developer documentation platform that helps companies and businesses build and maintain public-facing documentation (X, Coinbase, Anthropic, Scale AI, and over 20% of the last YC batch.
The team is full of people who are builders at heart and are genuinely passionate about elevating developer experiences. Our team is small but mighty (28 people, including 10 engineers) with over 10,000 companies using us.
We’re hiring all across the board - but in particular, we’re focusing on maturing our engineering organization and hiring more senior team members. If you’re ready to do impactful, hands-on work, we’re ready to chat. Apply at <a href="https://mintlify.com/careers">https://mintlify.com/careers</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:19:37 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45110823</link><dc:creator>hahnbee</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45110823</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45110823</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by michaelm244 in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Comulate | Senior Engineer (3+ YoE) | ONSITE in San Francisco, CA<p>We're building automation software for the $7T insurance industry, accelerated by AI. Seed stage in terms of headcount (~ 20 people) but Series B in terms of business traction (+ cash-flow positive). We've intentionally stayed under the radar.<p>- Product has caused customers to literally cry tears of joy<p>- Experienced eng team from Airbnb / Brex / LiveRamp<p>- Stack: TS, Postgres, React, GraphQL, and Next.js<p>Apply here: <a href="https://comulate.com/careers" rel="nofollow">https://comulate.com/careers</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 21:12:36 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45109131</link><dc:creator>michaelm244</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45109131</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45109131</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by theodoretliu in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Pocketflows | Founding Engineer | San Francisco, CA | In-person | $170k-225k + equity | pocketflows.com<p>At Pocketflows, we’re on a mission to help Main Street SMBs grow. We build marketing and communication APIs that embed inside the vertical SaaS platforms that businesses like salons, fitness studios, and restaurants already use to run their operations.<p>As a founding engineer, you'll be launching new marketing products in addition to our existing email, SMS, and review platform.<p>Our values blend ambition with kindness and empathy.<p>Stack: Ruby on Rails, React + TypeScript, TailwindCSS, Postgres, Redis<p>Interested? Email us at team@pocketflows.com with your resume/LinkedIn/GitHub, a note on why you'd like to join, and an answer to this riddle:<p>"I'm thinking of a secret number hidden on pocketflows.com. I won't console you if you can't figure it out"</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:48:50 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45108839</link><dc:creator>theodoretliu</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45108839</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45108839</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by trunksuzieross in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Trunk | <a href="https://trunk.io" rel="nofollow">https://trunk.io</a> | DevRel Engineer - Remote US or Canada|  Staff Full Stack Engineer | Sr Full Stack Engineer - San Francisco<p>Trunk is an a16z funded dev tools startup, redefining software development at scale. We aim to solve problems that developers hate by bringing the tools usually built in-house at the best engineering orgs to every development team. Some of our products:<p><pre><code>  * Merge Queue: a merge queue, to ensure that PRs are tested in order before they're merged.

  *Flaky Tests: Detect and eliminate Flaky Tests.

  * AI DevOps Assistant: Automate Reccurring DevOps tasks in chat.
</code></pre>
In 2022, we raised a $25M Series A led by Initialized Capital (Garry Tan) and a16z (Peter Levine)<p>Our tech stack:<p><pre><code>  * Frontend: Typescript, React, Redux, Next.js
  * Backend: Typescript, Node, AWS, CDK, k8s, gRPC
  * Observability: Prometheus, Grafana, Kiali, Jaeger
  * CLI: C++20, Bazel
  * VSCode Extension: Typescript
  * CI/CD: GitHub Actions
  * General: GitHub, Slack, Linear, Slite
</code></pre>
Unlimited PTO (and we all actually take PTO), competitive salary and equity packages! Please apply here: <a href="https://trunk.io/jobs" rel="nofollow">https://trunk.io/jobs</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:24:28 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45105226</link><dc:creator>trunksuzieross</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45105226</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45105226</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by dcsourcegraph in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Sourcegraph | San Francisco | Full-Time | SWE, Design Engineer, Forward Deployed Eng, Head of Design, Solutions Eng (all roles code) | <a href="https://sourcegraph.com" rel="nofollow">https://sourcegraph.com</a><p>Sourcegraph is hiring SWEs and FDEs for Amp (<a href="https://ampcode.com" rel="nofollow">https://ampcode.com</a>), the most effective multi-model AI coding agent. We're a team that ships and we build Amp in a crazy way (see <a href="https://ampcode.com/how-we-build" rel="nofollow">https://ampcode.com/how-we-build</a>). Backed by Sequoia, a16z, Craft Ventures, and Redpoint.<p>We’re hiring people who are doing impressive things with coding agents. If that's you, show us something you've built or published!</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:19:48 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45105141</link><dc:creator>dcsourcegraph</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45105141</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45105141</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by deyton in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>TestBox | <a href="https://www.testbox.com/career" rel="nofollow">https://www.testbox.com/career</a> | Multiple Roles | ONSITE San Francisco, CA | Full-time<p>TestBox is a fast-growing startup on a mission to fundamentally transform how software is bought and sold. We're building the next-generation infrastructure for software transactions, creating seamless experiences from initial interest to successful onboarding. We are backed by world-class investors and are looking for foundational team members to build greenfield systems and make a massive impact from day one.<p>I'm hiring manager for several key roles, onsite in San Francisco:<p>Senior Backend Engineer | $180k + Equity & Benefits | <a href="https://testbox.breezy.hr/p/cd4259566a98" rel="nofollow">https://testbox.breezy.hr/p/cd4259566a98</a><p>Senior Full-Stack Engineer (Frontend Focus) | $180k + Equity & Benefits | <a href="https://testbox.breezy.hr/p/df48b9667887" rel="nofollow">https://testbox.breezy.hr/p/df48b9667887</a><p>Senior Software Engineer, Applied AI | $180k + Equity & Benefits | <a href="https://testbox.breezy.hr/p/14fdbd0b561d" rel="nofollow">https://testbox.breezy.hr/p/14fdbd0b561d</a><p>Staff Technical Program Manager | $180k + Bonus, Equity, & Benefits | <a href="https://testbox.breezy.hr/p/c822a14a4103" rel="nofollow">https://testbox.breezy.hr/p/c822a14a4103</a><p>Senior Product Designer | $160k + Equity & Benefits | <a href="https://testbox.breezy.hr/p/9bca001ba1d6" rel="nofollow">https://testbox.breezy.hr/p/9bca001ba1d6</a><p>You can view all open positions and apply through our careers page: <a href="https://www.testbox.com/career" rel="nofollow">https://www.testbox.com/career</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:24:48 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45104290</link><dc:creator>deyton</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45104290</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45104290</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by kanjun in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Imbue | <a href="https://imbue.com" rel="nofollow">https://imbue.com</a> | Senior Product Engineers | Full-time | San Francisco, CA (ONSITE)<p>Imbue is building a coding agent environment (<a href="https://imbue.com/product/sculptor/" rel="nofollow">https://imbue.com/product/sculptor/</a>) that imbues engineering wisdom into LLM workflows—so anyone has the power to create software they can trust.<p>We aim to rekindle the dream of personal computing and make software creation accessible to all, so every person can have the power to shape their computational future.<p>For more example projects and benefits, see the full job description: <a href="https://imbue.com/careers" rel="nofollow">https://imbue.com/careers</a><p>Please apply through the website above. All submissions are reviewed by a real person!</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:13:06 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45104145</link><dc:creator>kanjun</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45104145</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45104145</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by snowmaker in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Y Combinator (yes, the people who run this site) | Full stack web and AI | San Francisco | Onsite | Fulltime<p>YC itself hires software engineers from time to time.  Many people don't know that YC has a small but very important software team.  We run several websites - not just this one, but also workatastartup.com (the main way YC companies hire), a social network for YC founders, and the core infrastructure that YC itself runs on.<p>Recently, we've been spending most of our time building our own AI agents.  Over the last year, YC has mostly funded AI agent companies, so it's been cool to go really deep building our own AI agents too.  We're building agents to automate every aspect of what we do, and pushing the limits of what's possible with the current models to do it.<p>An unusual aspect of being on the YC software team is that you'll get full access to the YC program, founders and partners.  The YC batch runs in the same building we work out of, so there are talks with famous founders happening most nights, right downstairs in our building.  If you want to start a startup someday, working at YC would be an excellent jumping off point - several YC companies have come from team members who decided to start their own company.<p>YC works fully in-person in SF. We're happy to help you move here if you're in the US already.  Unfortunately we can't sponsor new visas, but we're happy to transfer existing ones.<p>YC offers highly competitive compensation and benefits.<p>You can apply online (<a href="https://www.ycombinator.com/careers">https://www.ycombinator.com/careers</a>) or just email me at jared@ycombinator.com</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:22:38 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45100062</link><dc:creator>snowmaker</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45100062</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45100062</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by konstantina_ps in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Kaedim | Software Engineer, Machine Learning Engineer, Customer Support Engineer, Product Manager, Founding Recruiter | Onsite | Full-time | San Francisco, Singapore, London | US & UK Sponsorship Available Kaedim is an AI startup building ML algorithms that turn images into digital 3d models. We are a group of ~10 looking to grow the team to help streamline 3d content creation for 3d artists and are already working with 1 of the top 10 games of all time! Using our AI and in-house art team, we have the most accurate, game-ready 2d → 3d asset generation pipeline. Currently, we are offering a 10x speed up to 3D asset creation pipelines of 200+ game developers and we are working with partners like Voodoo, Upland, Azra Games.
Check out our demo here: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tlQWFG1DLb0" rel="nofollow">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tlQWFG1DLb0</a><p>Job descriptions and application link: <a href="https://join-kaedim.notion.site/" rel="nofollow">https://join-kaedim.notion.site/</a><p>Tech Stack:<p>Product (web app, API): React, MySQL, NodeJS, Python, AWS<p>Machine Learning: Python, PyTorch, AWS</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:52:14 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45099891</link><dc:creator>konstantina_ps</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45099891</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45099891</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by oc-max in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>OneCrew | Multiple Roles | ONSITE / HYBRID | San Francisco, CA<p>OneCrew is the leading unified platform helping paving contractors estimate accurately, manage crews effectively, and track profitability in real-time. We eliminate the costly mistakes and wasted time that come from juggling multiple disconnected systems—giving contractors a single source of truth to run their entire operation.<p>We recently closed our Series A and are looking for highly motivated individuals to own their domain and accelerate our growth.<p><pre><code>  - Engineering Manager
  - 3x Software Engineers (Fullstack, Frontend, Backend)
  - Product Manager
  - Growth
</code></pre>
Find job details here: <a href="https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/onecrew" rel="nofollow">https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/onecrew</a> and apply via email: hn [at] getonecrew [dot] com</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 04:00:11 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45099009</link><dc:creator>oc-max</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45099009</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45099009</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by zoetrope in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>zoetro.pe | Technical Staff | San Francisco, CA | ONSITE/REMOTE | Full-time<p>We're an applied lab building deterministic and deep generative experiences. Our team has built AI models, games, and infrastucture at Tesla Autopilot, Epic Games, Scale.ai, Repl.it, Bun, and Lucasarts.<p>You will be building procedural simulation models and the supporting infrastructure and applications. We're a small team, so this means everything from CUDA kernels and Pytorch notebooks to web-apps. Our stack is multi-lingual and spans from very low to very high level code. We use both our own models and external providers.<p>Our team is hybrid-remote, being primarily based in San Francisco.<p>Our stack: Python (Pytorch/jax), Typescript(React etc), Rust/C++, Ghidra<p>We're looking for exceptional research engineers who aren't afraid to get their hands dirty. Experience with computational geometry or compilers/language design/formal methods is a plus.<p>Formal qualifications are less important than passion and skill. We're building our dreams, we hope you will feel the same.<p>If interested, email me at: simon+hn@zoetro.pe</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:12:10 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45098095</link><dc:creator>zoetrope</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45098095</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45098095</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by vedhsaka in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>April | <a href="https://www.tryapril.com">https://www.tryapril.com</a> | San Francisco /Gurgaon, India | ONSITE | Full-time<p><pre><code>  Roles:
  1. Head of Growth (SF)
  2. Senior Software Engineer (Gurgaon, India)
</code></pre>
We're building voice-first AI executive assistants for email and calendar management—think having a real assistant who actually gets things done. Backed by Y Combinator and other investors, we're at an extremely early stage and moving fast to hire our growth lead and early engineering team.<p>Head of Growth - Own the 0→100K user journey. Build content-led growth across LinkedIn/X/TikTok, run viral B2C experiments, and craft our brand voice. We need a proven track record of growing consumer products, content creation chops, and unreasonable excitement about retention curves. Extremely competitive salary + equity + user milestone bonuses.<p>Senior Software Engineer - Build the core backend for our AI assistant. 2-6 years of experience, TypeScript/Python, with consumer product background preferred. Work directly with founders on architecture decisions. Must work from the office. Competitive salary + early equity + quarterly performance hikes.<p>If you're interested, send your profile to akash@tryapril.com</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:54:38 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45097684</link><dc:creator>vedhsaka</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45097684</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45097684</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by josephstein in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>VeritusAgent | <a href="https://www.veritusagent.ai">https://www.veritusagent.ai</a> | Full Stack Software Engineer | Hybrid - San Francisco | Full-time | $200k + 0.5% - 1%<p>We started two months ago and our AI agents are already live and making calls! We're scaling fast and hiring a full stack engineer to join our team in-person in SF<p><a href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/veritus-agent/jobs/cvHQbJy-full-stack-engineer">https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/veritus-agent/jobs/cvH...</a><p>Reach out to me directly!</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 22:09:56 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45097042</link><dc:creator>josephstein</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45097042</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45097042</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by jhirshman in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Uncountable | NY, SF, London & Munich (In-Person) | Full-Stack Engineering<p><a href="https://www.uncountable.com/hiring/hn" rel="nofollow">https://www.uncountable.com/hiring/hn</a><p>Uncountable accelerates R&D for industrial scientists across leading materials, chemicals, and life sciences organizations. With our SaaS solution, our customers get better products to the market in half the time. Uncountable was founded by MIT and Stanford engineers and has been profitable since 2016. Our team has grown from 50 to 100 over the last two years.<p>Full-Stack Engineers | $120k - $220k + Equity<p>---> Uncountable is looking for engineers who can spearhead the development of the Uncountable Web Platform. The position is heavily product-driven and comes with challenges across the stack.<p>--> Summer internships and working student positions are also available.<p>Learn more: <a href="https://www.uncountable.com/hiring/hn" rel="nofollow">https://www.uncountable.com/hiring/hn</a><p>Uncountable is hiring in New York City, San Francisco, London, and Munich.<p>Contact our CTO directly at jason@uncountable.com</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096995</link><dc:creator>jhirshman</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096995</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096995</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by jamgraham in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Come work with me @ AllTrails and help lead our full-stack, frontend, backend, and mobile teams.<p>Role: Director of Engineering — AllTrails (San Francisco / Remote)<p>About Us:
AllTrails is the most trusted platform for outdoor exploration, helping millions of people discover and enjoy trails every day. We’re consistently ranked among the top Health & Fitness apps and were named Apple’s App of the Year in 2023.<p>Role Overview:
You’ll lead multiple engineering teams across the stack, set technical strategy, and work closely with product and design to deliver a high-quality experience for our global community.<p>What We’re Looking For:
• 10+ years of software engineering experience, with 5+ years in engineering leadership
• Experience managing multi-disciplinary teams (frontend, backend, mobile)
• Strength in technical architecture, team development, and cross-functional collaboration<p>Compensation & Benefits:
• Competitive salary, equity, comprehensive benefits, unlimited PTO, monthly “Trail Days,” and a collaborative, mission-driven culture.</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 21:45:47 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096910</link><dc:creator>jamgraham</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096910</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096910</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by wilson090 in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>CreativeMode (S24) | <a href="https://creativemode.net">https://creativemode.net</a> | On-site - San Francisco, CA<p>CreativeMode is building Lovable for video game mods, starting with Minecraft. In our first three months, we built the most powerful no-code modding platform ever for Minecraft and created a double digit percentage of all mods ever released. We're building an entirely new category of gaming tools. Minecraft is only the beginning.<p>We're hiring a Founding Engineer who wants to build at the intersection of tech and gaming. Ideal candidates have a passion for the category and have experience building production-level LLM/AI applications or are killer full-stack engineers who can own product features end to end.<p>Ideally 3+ years of experience<p>Email me at wilson@creativemode.net with your resume and a short blurb on why you'd like to join the team.</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 21:26:08 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096769</link><dc:creator>wilson090</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096769</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096769</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by mdahardy in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Roundtable | <a href="https://roundtable.ai">https://roundtable.ai</a> | On-site San Francisco, CA | Full-time<p>Roundtable is a research and deployment company building the proof-of-human layer in digital identity. Roundtable seeks to research and build real-world Turing Tests, and to productize these developments in bot detection, fraud prevention, and continuous authentication.<p>We're hiring a Member of Technical Staff. This is not a typical “Founding Engineer” position. In particular, this role will involve more research than similar positions. You should be prepared to spend around half of your time on research and half on engineering.<p>The ideal candidate has experience in both. However, we don’t strictly require research experience as long as you have a strong quantitative background and an eagerness to learn. We do require proficiency in both web development (Javascript, Node.js) and Python.<p>If you're interested shoot an email to matt@roundtable.ai with your resume and a short blurb on why you're interested (note: we are unable to offer visa sponsorship at this time).</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 21:11:54 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096644</link><dc:creator>mdahardy</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096644</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096644</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by shuluster in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Loop | loop.com | Engineering, Product | On-site San Francisco, CA, Chicago, IL<p>Loop is on a mission to unlock profits trapped in the supply chain (<a href="https://www.loop.com/article/unlock-profit-trapped-in-your-supply-chain" rel="nofollow">https://www.loop.com/article/unlock-profit-trapped-in-your-s...</a>) and lower costs for consumers. Bad data and inefficient workflows create friction that limits working capital and raises costs for every supply chain stakeholder.<p>Loop’s modern transportation cost management platform uses our domain-driven AI to harness the complexity of supply chain data and documentation. We improve transportation spend visibility so companies can control their costs and power profit. That is why industry leaders like Nvidia, Verizon, Dell, J.P. Morgan Chase, ABB, Estee Lauder, Tyson Foods, Yeti and Olipop, work with Loop.<p>1. Raised $100m+ from JPM GEP, Founders Fund, 8VC, Susa Ventures, Flexport, Index.<p>2. 250+ paying enterprise customers with multiple-year contracts.<p>3. High-caliber team of engineers and operators from Google, Scale AI, Flexport, Uber, Rakuten, Square, Meta, Stanford, Brown, Princeton, and Yale.<p>Fullstack Engineer San Francisco - <a href="https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/loop/jobs/4102236004" rel="nofollow">https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/loop/jobs/4102236004</a><p>Fullstack Engineer Chicago - <a href="https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/loop/jobs/4830548004" rel="nofollow">https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/loop/jobs/4830548004</a><p>AI Engineer San Francisco - <a href="https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/loop/jobs/5391540004" rel="nofollow">https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/loop/jobs/5391540004</a><p>Product Manager, San Francisco - <a href="https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/loop/jobs/5602148004" rel="nofollow">https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/loop/jobs/5602148004</a><p>Engineering Director, San Francisco - <a href="https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/loop/jobs/5597686004" rel="nofollow">https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/loop/jobs/5597686004</a><p>Other roles at <a href="https://www.loop.com/company/careers" rel="nofollow">https://www.loop.com/company/careers</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 20:46:46 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096468</link><dc:creator>shuluster</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096468</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096468</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by dvrp in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>krea.ai | Distributed Systems Eng. & Data Engineers | San Francisco (on-site), CA<p>I'm the cofounder & CTO of Krea (<a href="https://www.krea.ai" rel="nofollow">https://www.krea.ai</a>).<p>We are a startup in San Francisco building browser-based AI creative tools to improve the workflows of artists, designers, and professional creatives.<p>Small team (~20); millions of active users; and raised over $83M from top Silicon Valley investment firms.<p>We're looking for talented engineers who want to tackle hard technical challenges with smart people while building a creative platform that big companies and startups will rely on.<p>The job:<p>- Build distributed systems to process massive (billions of files, petabytes), amounts of image, video, and 3D data, solving scaling bottlenecks as you go.<p>- Build data pipelines and deploy ML models to make sense of raw data (e.g. find clean scenes within videos).<p>- Learn ML engineering from world-class researchers on a small tight-knit team.  As you’re building data pipelines, you’ll contribute to foundation image, video, and world models from 0 → production, and see them used by millions of Krea users.<p>- Play with massive amounts of compute on huge Kubernetes GPU clusters; our main GPU cluster takes up an entire datacenter from our provider.<p>Tech stack: python, pytorch, k8s, a rotating cast of data tools (e.g.  DuckDB, massive relational DBs, PyArrow, etc.)<p>You should apply if you are an excellent generalist engineer with strong backend experience and an intuition for systems design. Bonus points for deep experience with distributed systems, kubernetes, and existing ML or data experience (but not required!).  Cool side projects are a green flag.<p>A few links about us:<p>- <i>Sneak peek of our real-time video model → <a href="https://x.com/krea_ai/status/1961074072487620635" rel="nofollow">https://x.com/krea_ai/status/1961074072487620635</a></i><p>- <i>Technical report for FLUX.1 Krea, our first open-source text-to-image model → <a href="https://krea.ai/blog/flux-krea-open-source-release" rel="nofollow">https://krea.ai/blog/flux-krea-open-source-release</a></i><p>- <i>HN discussion around FLUX.1 Krea → <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44745555">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44745555</a></i><p>You can contact me at:<p><pre><code>  d+hn@krea.ai
</code></pre>
<i>(the +hn will bump your email in my inbox)</i></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 20:28:17 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096338</link><dc:creator>dvrp</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096338</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45096338</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by n2d4 in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Stack Auth (S24) | San Francisco, CA | Full-time<p>Hiring founding & design engineers!<p>We're building the customer platform for developers — think of a single service that does auth, payments, analytics, marketing emails, and so much more. We're selling to developers & startups so our audience is right here on this website!<p>If you're in San Francisco and frequent Hacker News, that's enough of a reason to DM me on Twitter @konstiwohlwend. Would love to invite you over for a coffee at our hacker house!<p>If you apply, please send me a few recent HN threads that you enjoyed :)<p>konsti@stack-auth.com | <a href="https://stack-auth.com">https://stack-auth.com</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:30:42 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45095319</link><dc:creator>n2d4</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45095319</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45095319</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by mceoin in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Sourcetable.com | Product Marketing (contract) | San Francisco
We're building a spreadsheet-based operating system for the web, although on first touch Sourcetable feels more like Excel Copilot or "Cursor for spreadsheets".<p>We're looking for one Product Marketer to join our team in a part-time contract capacity in the Bay Area (San Francisco preferred). The requirement are that you need to be great at video storytelling and also be strong at spreadsheets & analysis.<p>Everyone on our team codes, and you should too. There's no technical requirement for the role, per-se, but we have found it is better this way.<p>Email me if this sounds interesting.</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:15:55 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45095180</link><dc:creator>mceoin</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45095180</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45095180</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by azmaty in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Talk Machine | Founding Engineers | Remote (or London, Dubai, San Francisco) | <a href="https://talkmachine.com/jobs" rel="nofollow">https://talkmachine.com/jobs</a><p>Hello. I’m the founder of Talk Machine, previously founded Citymapper.<p>We’re working on building a consumer voice product / platform using AI, driven by the mission to improve human communication.<p>Our application process is unique. Just go to <a href="https://talkmachine.com/jobs" rel="nofollow">https://talkmachine.com/jobs</a> and send us a voice note and we can begin talking, just like we met in person.<p>We have 2 specific posts, <a href="https://talkmachine.com/jobs/engineer" rel="nofollow">https://talkmachine.com/jobs/engineer</a> for full stack founding engineers and <a href="https://talkmachine.com/jobs/mobile" rel="nofollow">https://talkmachine.com/jobs/mobile</a> for iOS/Android, but glad to hear from anyone that loves the product/category.<p>We’re seed funded and can pay competitively + quality stock options (EMI in UK).<p>You like: talking, consumer, voice, AI, small fast teams, building great products, chasing product market fit<p>You can also reach out to me at <a href="https://talkmachine.com/az" rel="nofollow">https://talkmachine.com/az</a>. :)</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:02:07 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45095049</link><dc:creator>azmaty</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45095049</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45095049</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by jkubicek in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Stitch Fix | Data Platform Engineer | Full-time | Remote (though we do have an office in San Francisco) | <a href="https://www.stitchfix.com/careers/jobs" rel="nofollow">https://www.stitchfix.com/careers/jobs</a><p>I'm the hiring manager for two roles on our Data Platform team at Stitch Fix, one at the lead level, one at the principal level. Here's the blurb from our job postings, but feel free to reach out to me directly if you have any questions! jim.kubicek AT stitchfix.com<p>> The Data Platform team builds the foundation that powers everything from Stitch Fix's signature personalization to our most cutting-edge AI innovations. We exist to make our data scientists and engineers wildly productive - by delivering fast, flexible, and trusted infrastructure that fuels experimentation, recommendations, insights, and a new generation of AI/ML-powered experiences.<p>* <a href="https://www.stitchfix.com/careers/jobs?gh_jid=6819981&gh_jid=6819981" rel="nofollow">https://www.stitchfix.com/careers/jobs?gh_jid=6819981&gh_jid...</a><p>* <a href="https://www.stitchfix.com/careers/jobs?gh_jid=6750033&gh_jid=6750033" rel="nofollow">https://www.stitchfix.com/careers/jobs?gh_jid=6750033&gh_jid...</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:43:55 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45094884</link><dc:creator>jkubicek</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45094884</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45094884</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by amacneil in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Foxglove | Onsite or Remote | Full Time or Contract | <a href="https://foxglove.dev/" rel="nofollow">https://foxglove.dev/</a><p>Foxglove is observability for robotics and physical AI. We accelerate robotics developers with logging, data management, and multimodal visualization. We're well funded (Series A, ~40 people) and assembling the most talented team in the industry to build a platform for all robots. Sound interesting? Join us!<p>Hiring across a number of roles, in San Francisco and some remote.<p>- Senior/Staff Frontend Engineer (typescript, react, webgl, rust, wasm)<p>- Senior/Staff Backend Engineer (rust)<p>- Senior/Staff Backend Engineer (rust, remote - Australia/NZ time zone)<p>- Senior/Staff Product Engineer (full stack typescript)<p>- Account Executive<p>- Forward-Deployed Engineer, Frontend<p>- Forward-Deployed Engineer, Backend<p>- Solutions Engineer, Robotics<p>- Dev Relations, Physical AI<p>Bonus points if you have prior experience at a top AV or robotics company.<p>*Remote friendly*: All roles are open to remote for experienced candidates (staff-level or prior experience at a top AV or robotics company)<p>Customer-facing roles outside of SF are remote but we are looking for candidates in those cities who can travel to customer sites.<p><a href="https://foxglove.dev/careers" rel="nofollow">https://foxglove.dev/careers</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:16:03 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45094601</link><dc:creator>amacneil</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45094601</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45094601</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by Redeker_15_Beep in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Temporal Technologies | Multiple positions in United States - WORK FROM HOME | FULL-TIME |<p>Temporal offers an entirely new way to build scalable and reliable applications. Temporal enables developers to focus on writing important business logic, and not on managing state or worrying about the underlying infrastructure. Sequoia Capital led our last round of funding and our team has experience from start-ups and larger companies like Microsoft, Google, Amazon, Uber, and more.<p>Temporal’s Series C Funding Announcement: <a href="https://temporal.io/blog/temporal-series-c-announcement" rel="nofollow">https://temporal.io/blog/temporal-series-c-announcement</a><p>Temporal in 7 minutes: <a href="https://temporal.io/tldr" rel="nofollow">https://temporal.io/tldr</a><p>We're looking for senior level engineers for multiple roles - see here - <a href="https://www.temporal.io/careers" rel="nofollow">https://www.temporal.io/careers</a><p>FEATURED ROLES:<p>Senior Developer Success Engineer → <a href="https://grnh.se/ed5cec6a7us" rel="nofollow">https://grnh.se/ed5cec6a7us</a><p>Staff Software Engineer, Traffic → <a href="https://grnh.se/1cbb896d7us" rel="nofollow">https://grnh.se/1cbb896d7us</a><p>Staff Software Engineer, Cloud Infrastructure → <a href="https://grnh.se/8b0ba8347us" rel="nofollow">https://grnh.se/8b0ba8347us</a><p>Staff Developer Advocate, AI - San Francisco → <a href="https://grnh.se/00dec64f7us" rel="nofollow">https://grnh.se/00dec64f7us</a><p>Senior Product Manager, Cloud Scalability & Capacity → <a href="https://grnh.se/6a766cv77us" rel="nofollow">https://grnh.se/6a766cv77us</a><p>Senior Software Engineer, Developer Productivity → <a href="https://grnh.se/jdr272cz7us" rel="nofollow">https://grnh.se/jdr272cz7us</a><p>Staff Software Engineer - Cloud Capacity → <a href="https://grnh.se/a0hc6o6h7us" rel="nofollow">https://grnh.se/a0hc6o6h7us</a><p>US benefits include: Unlimited PTO, 12 Holidays + 2 Floating Holidays, 100% Premiums Coverage for Medical, Dental, and Vision, AD&D, LT & ST Disability and Life Insurance , Empower 401K Plan, Additional Perks for Learning & Development, Lifestyle Spending, In-Home Office Setup, Professional Memberships, WFH Meals, Internet Stipend and more! Benefits outside the United States vary by country.<p>Apply here <a href="https://www.temporal.io/careers/" rel="nofollow">https://www.temporal.io/careers/</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:13:31 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45093960</link><dc:creator>Redeker_15_Beep</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45093960</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45093960</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by MeaningfulAI in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>PUNTT.AI |Founding AI-First Growth Marketer | Founding AE | Full-time | Hybrid in New York or San Francisco<p>Our mission is to kill the review. Free people to do meaningful work.<p>Founding Account Executive: Work directly with the Founders and CEO to help build and own our GTM motion from the ground up. If you're excited about building in public, owning revenue from zero to one, and working directly with founders—you’ll thrive here.<p>Ideal profile:
 - 2–5 years in B2B SaaS sales or agency partnerships. Experience selling into marketing or creative teams is a big plus.<p>More info & apply  <a href="https://wellfound.com/jobs/3340879" rel="nofollow">https://wellfound.com/jobs/3340879</a><p>Founding AI Growth Marketer: drive early pipeline and positioning. You’ll work directly with the CEO and own everything from narrative → campaign execution → GTM growth experiments.<p>Ideal profile:
 - 4–8 years experience in B2B SaaS, creative tech, or growth marketing. Strong writing chops, creative instincts, and a bias for speed.<p>More info & apply  <a href="https://wellfound.com/jobs/3349975" rel="nofollow">https://wellfound.com/jobs/3349975</a></p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 15:22:59 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45093443</link><dc:creator>MeaningfulAI</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45093443</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45093443</guid></item><item><title><![CDATA[New comment by revere in "Ask HN: Who is hiring? (September 2025)"]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<p>Revere Defense Technologies - Autonomous Networks and Infrastructure<p>San Francisco (Dogpatch) | On-site w/ flexibility | Full-time | Multiple Roles, $120k–220k + equity + benefits<p>Why: Comms are contested. Radios make you a target, satellites aren’t guaranteed, and brittle legacy networks won’t survive future fights.<p>What: We’re building an autonomous maritime network — think distributed systems in the ocean—extending resilient comms, sensing and compute to the edge in high-threat remote environments.<p>Who we are looking for:<p>- Software Engineers: large-scale distributed systems, networking, system design, embedded software, DevOps rollouts. Python, C++, Rust. Bonus: SDR, mesh, security.<p>- Electrical Engineers: PCB layout, embedded, RF, circuits, power/batteries, electro-mechanical. Bonus: DSP.<p>- Marine/Mechanical Engineers: pressure vessels, subsea robotics, gliders, ruggedized design; DFM, reliability, field deployment.<p>You will: ship code to robots, test on the water, move fast, own big surface area, and work directly with military operators.<p>About Us: Our founding team includes a Navy SEAL veteran, defense industry engineers, builders, hackers, and watermen (sailors, boaters, divers, fishermen). We’re focused on real future missions — not legacy requirements. Venture-backed; public launch soon.<p>Eligibility for a TS/SCI security clearance is a plus. Please send a short note + resume/portfolio to jobs@reveredefense.co with subject HN – Engineering.</p>
]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 15:03:32 +0000</pubDate><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45093219</link><dc:creator>revere</dc:creator><comments>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45093219</comments><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45093219</guid></item></channel></rss>